<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Application on Monochrome</title>
    <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/categories/application/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Application on Monochrome</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/categories/application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/guide/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/guide/configuration/</guid>
      <description>This guide assumes you are starting with the configuration of the quick start (demo) site. It only describes the options the theme provides, not which Hugo options should be set for the theme to work.
Site Configuration To set a favicon, use the params.site.favicon option. Make sure the location does not start with / to avoid Hugo URL resolution quirks.
To set which section (or page) is rendered as the index, use the params.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/guide/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/guide/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>By the end of this guide you should have a Hugo site ready to be generated.
Quick Start Site The theme has a quickstart-site archive for every release. The archive contains a demo blog ready with the theme already set up inside.
Head over to the theme&amp;rsquo;s releases on Github and download the quickstart-site archive of the latest version.
After downloading, extract the quickstart site into an empty directory. The site should be ready to build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Optimization</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/guide/seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Monochrome/guide/seo/</guid>
      <description>The theme includes structured data for search engine optimization. Make sure to configure all options correctly to achieve the best results.
Site Configuration Configuring the site title and author(s) in the site configuration are required for the structured data to be correctly formed.
title = &amp;#34;Hugo Themes&amp;#34; [author] name = &amp;#34;Steve Francia&amp;#34; A description, organization logo and default article images are also required.
The organization logo params.seo.logo image must be in either JPG or PNG format, and sized 600px wide and 60px high.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>